{
  "categories": [],
  "description": "Name the brand for each selected car model.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Volkswagen",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Beetle"
  }, {
    "answer": "Honda",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Accord"
  }, {
    "answer": "Toyota",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Corolla"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chevrolet",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Corvette"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jeep",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Cherokee"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dodge",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Viper"
  }, {
    "answer": "Porsche",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "911 Carrera"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nissan",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Maxima"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ford",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Crown Victoria"
  }, {
    "answer": "Cadillac",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Escalade"
  }, {
    "answer": "Kia",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Sportage"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hyundai",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Elantra"
  }, {
    "answer": "Pontiac",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Grand Am"
  }, {
    "answer": "Subaru",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Outback"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bugatti",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Veyron"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lincoln",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Navigator"
  }, {
    "answer": "Buick",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "LeSabre"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mitsubishi",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Galant"
  }, {
    "answer": "Oldsmobile",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Cutlass"
  }, {
    "answer": "Saturn",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Ion"
  }, {
    "answer": "AMC",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "Gremlin"
  }, {
    "answer": "BMW",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "745i"
  }, {
    "answer": "Audi",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "A4"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hummer",
    "category": "Car Brands Quiz",
    "question": "H3"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Car Brands Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/car-brands-quiz.php"
}